Guide to the Ethical Culture Fieldston School Records 1879-2017 MS 3042
New-York Historical Society
- Record Group 14. Photographs (1882-2016; 62.97 linear feet), 216997; 62.97 Linear feet
  - Series III. Photographs after 1980, 1980-2012; 23.5 Linear feet
    - Unidentified negatives (7 folders), undated (Offsite-box 258, Folder 15-21)
    - Various photographs (3 folders), 1997-2012 (Offsite-box 258, Folder 22-24)
      Includes 125th Anniversary event and engraved 2012 Fieldston frame with photograph of building.
  - Series IV. Communications collections, circa 1990s-2010s; 6 Linear feet
    This series contains groups of materials collected by ECFS users for a particular purpose in alumni affairs, publications, or the communications department. The majority of photographs are of students, faculty, events, and alumni. Some other photographs used for communications purposes can also be found throughout Series III. Photographs after 1980.
    This series begins with Alumni Office photographs, followed by photographs collected for publications, and photographs collected for communications purposes.
    - Alumni Office collection (22 folders), circa 1990s-2010s (Offsite-box 219, Folder 1-22)
      Snapshots of students (mostly high school level), alumni, faculty and staff, and the campus. Student photos are mostly of events such as holidays, pep rallies, and fashion shows. Some photographs include notes or identifying information. The majority of photographs date circa 2008-2012.
    - Alumni Office collection (8 folders), 1997-2008 (Offsite-box 258, Folder 1-8)
      Photographs sent to the school by alumni, often with identifiying information or correspondence. Also student and alumni event photographs.
    - Publications - ECS Reporter (7 folders), circa 1990s (Offsite-box 218, Folder 15-21)
      Photos of students, sports, faculty, and alumni for use in the ECS Reporter publication.
    - Publications - Various for Field Notes (3 folders), circa 2003 (Offsite-box 221, Folder 13-15)
      Faculty and staff, student life, athletics, and events for all schools.
    - Publications - Various, circa 1990s (Offsite-box 253)
      Black and white photographs of students, activities, and campus, marked for possible use in publications.
    - Publications - Various (12 folders), 1998-2002 (Offsite-box 226, Folder 5-16)
      Various photographs collected for the ECS Reporter, Field Notes, and other publications.
    - Communications - Fieldston arts and student life (15 folders), circa 2000s (Offsite-box 223, Folder 1-15)
      Includes images of Cory Booker as speaker at 2006 graduation ceremony.
    - Communications - Faculty, staff, and administration candids (2 folders), circa 2000s (Offsite-box 223, Folder 16-17)
    - Communications - Midtown and various elementary school (18 folders), circa 2000s (Offsite-box 224, Folder 1-18)
    - Communications - Fieldston Lower (5 folders), circa 2000s (Offsite-box 225, Folder 1-5)
    - Communications - Portraits (13 folders), circa 2000s (Offsite-box 225, Folder 6-18)
      Professional portraits of faculty, staff, administration, students and families.
    - Communications - Miscellaneous (4 folders), circa 2000s (Offsite-box 226, Folder 1-4)
  - Series V. Oversize materials and special formats, 1882-2012; 9.67 Linear feet
    This series contains oversize materials.
    Materials are arranged loosely by subject matter and chronology.
    - Pre-1928 oversize photographs, 1882-1927 (Offsite-box 262)
      Photograph of "laying of the cornerstone" for the Workingman's School and Free Kindergarten (1882). Eight pre-1928 Ethical Culture School boys sports team photographs (1909-1919). Ice hockey game (pre-1928). Class photographs (circa 1917-1919, undated). Collection of class of 1927 portraits, with students identified (circa 1927).
    - Student and faculty oversize photographs, circa 1950s-1990s (Offsite-box 261)
      Elementary student images pasted on three boards (1952-1957). Cut-out portraits of administration, faculty, and staff, on board with names identified (circa mid-twentieth century). Fieldston Lower and Midtown students (circa mid-twentieth century). Fieldston student and faculty group photos, including trips to Washington D.C. (1963-1995, undated).
    - Oversize reproductions of photographs, 1997, undated (Offsite-box 263)
      Reproductions (enlargements and color photocopies) of early photographs, some matted (undated). Also two display panals with reproductions of class of 1942 portraits, for 1997 reunion.
    - Various oversize photographs, circa 1990s (Offsite-box 264)
      Original photographs and mock-ups for class of 1947 50th reunion publication (1997). Black and white photographs labeled "pictures from reception room and various student portraits and candid photographs (circa 1990s). Graphic design"mechanicals" for printed materials, circa twentieth century (non-photographic, circa 1990s).
    - Various oversize photographs (6 folders), 1970-2002, undated (Offsite-box 265, Folder 1-6)
      Tate Library photographs and ephemera, 1970. Expo '71 photographs, 1971. Fieldston Class of 2000 scrapbook, 1996-2000. Various contact sheets, 2001-2002. Miscellaneous undated photographs.
    - Slides - various (11 folders), 1964-1996, undated (Offsite-box 297, Folder 1-11)
      Various student life and events, mostly from Fieldston Lower and Fieldston, along with Tate Library construction (1968-1969). Also includes slides from presentation given to evaluators from the Middle Atlantic Independent schools accrediting agency, with list of slides and text of presentation. (See also audio recording of presentation, in Box 293.).
    - Slides - Fieldston sports (17 folders), 1992-1996 (Offsite-box 297, Folder 12-18)
    - Slides - capital campaigns (5 folders), 1986, 1995, 2000 (Offsite-box 297, Folder 19-24)
    - Slides - Fieldston various, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 296)
      6 small boxes.
    - Slides - Fieldston library construction, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 296)
      3 small boxes.
    - Slides - Fieldston outs, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 296)
      17 small boxes with various of student life. Also includes one box Midtown outs.
    - Slides - Fieldston slide show, 1985 (Offsite-box 296)
      2 small boxes, Tray A and Tray C.
    - Slides - Fieldston sports, 1994 (Offsite-box 296)
      4 small boxes.
    - Slides - senior slide show, 1988 (Offsite-box 296)
      7 small boxes.
    - Slides - various, 1979-1983, undated (Offsite-box 296)
      8 small boxes. Fieldston Lower School second grade, 1979. Amish trip, 1980. Wolf visit assembly/Racoon in tree, 1983. Five unlabeled.
    - Slides - student art work, undated (Offsite-box 296)
      Slides of art work created by students from "nursery" through grade six. Slides in original box but not in original order. Label on box illegible.
    - Microfilm - School and Home, 2012 (Offsite-box 294)
      35mm microfilm silver halide duplicate negatives in 4 reels, for 1918-1937 issues of School and Home (print copies found in Record Group 11: Print matter). Created by Hudson Microimaging in 2012.
    - Negative spool - play or festival, undated (Offsite-box 294)
      Cardboard spool with negative, labeled "play or festival, bl + white."
    - Various materials - 75th Anniversary, 1953 (Offsite-box 296)
      Slides, negatives, and two film strips related to the school's 75th anniversary.
- Record Group 15. (RESTRICTED) Audiovisual (1950s-2008, undated; 26.42 linear feet), 216999; 26.42 Linear feet
  The Audiovisual record group contains audio or moving visual recordings. Types of materials include film reels, audio tape, cassette tapes, VHS and other video cassettes, and vinyl records. The title or identifier for each individual item is listed in this inventory.
  The majority of content has been captured by amateurs, such as school employees, with some professional recordings. For all materials in this record group, audio and visual content has been identified solely by labels or other written description accompanying objects (not by playback).
  Series I. Film
  Series II. VHS
  Series III. Audio recordings
  - Series I. Film, 1958-1986, undated; 4.5 Linear feet
    This series contains film reels, including Super 8 format (noted at the file level). A small number of earlier films have been converted to video, and can be found in Series II.
    - Guild festivals, 1943? (Offsite-box 348)
    - Anniversary film Part I / Third Grade Cook-out - October 1954 (Offsite-box 348)
    - Fieldston Lower - Indian film, 1958 (Offsite-box 349)
    - Fieldston football, 1959-1970, undated (Offsite-box 346)
      21 reels of film, with previous inventory in box (which includes some reels in box 347. Dated reels are labeled: Trinity vs. EMA, 1959 (2 rolls); Fieldston vs. Friends, 1961 (2 rolls); Fieldston vs. Carteret, 1962; Fieldston vs. Brunswick, 1965; Fieldston vs. Locust Valley, 1965 (2 rolls); Fieldston vs. Collegiate, 1970 (color); Fieldston vs. Brunswick, 1970 (color). Undated reels are labeled: Fieldston vs. Trinity (2 reels) and a third reel of a different Trinity game; Fieldston vs. Englewood (2 rolls); Fieldston vs. Woodmere; Fieldston vs. Locust Valley. There are also 4 unlabeled reels, but detached labels in the box suggest that one of these is Fieldston vs. McBurney and another is Fieldston vs. Locust Valley, 1967 ("with George Martens, faculty member"). A third is possibly St. Bernard's (1960), listed on the original inventory as poor, and the fourth may be another Woodmere.
    - Fieldston football, 1978-1979, undated (Offsite-box 347)
      Continuation of film reels from original inventory list in box 346. This box holds 5 undated reels: Fieldston H.S. (2 rolls); Fieldston School (2 rolls), and one unlabeled roll. Also, two Sony video cassettes from 1979: Fieldston vs. Englewood and Fieldston vs. Dalton. Also a third Sony videotape dated 11/10/78 with unclear label.
    - Ducky Wucky/graduation (Super 8), 1973, 1977 (Offsite-box 348)
      CBS Television Network Recording Operations label. Ducky Wucky, 1973, for graduation, 1977.
    - Various (Super 8), 1979-1986, undated (Offsite-box 347)
      10 small boxes of Kodachrome Super 8 film (one empty). Labeled with various subject, several with student animation projects.
    - Fieldston Lower art (Super 8), 1980-1981, undated (Offsite-box 347)
      Two Kodak reels. One box labeled Beluga Whale, undated. One box labeled Beowulf movie 5th Grade, 1980-1981.
    - Leonardo's Children: "Ethical Culture Fieldston School" (Missing Oct 2019), 1986
      Master tape. VHS copy also in collection. (Included in initial inventory during processing in June 2019, but not found in final boxing in October 2019.)
    - Fieldston - Indians, undated (Offsite-box 348)
      Note: "CUT WKPRNT."
    - Hand and Mind, undated (Offsite-box 349)
      Notes: Prepared by the students and faculty of Fieldston Lower. Brought by Toby 2007.
    - Anniversary film part II, undated (Offsite-box 348)
      Reel 8.
    - Fieldston anniversary, part II, undated (Offsite-box 348)
    - Saint Series - Dr. Radist, undated (Offsite-box 349)
      ITC Entertainment label for series "Saint Series" and episode "Gentle Ladies." Handwritten label of "Dr. Radist" on edge (possibly Howard Radest, Education Director 1979-1991).
    - Bears (Single 8), undated (Offsite-box 347)
      One small box of Fuji Single 8 film, labeled "bears."
    - 4th grade fair (Super 8), undated (Offsite-box 347)
      With note, Taken by Camile McDonald, IA teacher.
    - Various (Super 8), undated (Offsite-box 347)
      F.P Animations - Whitney - (Tests) - Western Landscape F.P.
    - Unlabeled loose roll (Super 8), undated (Offsite-box 347)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Offsite-box 348)
      In Motion Picture Enterprises, Inc. box, with note "on 1/P.U."
    - Unlabeled, undated (Offsite-box 348)
    - Unlabeled, undated (Offsite-box 348)
      In Stuyvesant Town Camera Shop can.
  - Series II. Video, 1972-2008; 16.5 Linear feet
    This series contains video cassettes—nearly all in VHS format, with some examples of Sony U-matic, Sony V-30H, Sony Beta II, and Sony Betacamp SP. The majority of content relates to special events and student performances, such as recitals, assemblies, and dance and drama performances. Content is identified based on titles written (usually by hand) on cassettes. Several video cases also include ephemera from related performances or events.
    This series begins with VHS cassettes of elementary school footage, followed by special events, and Fieldston Upper footage, and other programs and miscellaneous footage. VHS cassettes are followed by other video formats.
    - Midtown Ethical - closing assemblies, graduating classes, 1986-2003 (Offsite-box 275)
      Closing assembly, 1986 (2), 1987, 1988, 1989, and 1994. Ethical Culture School, 1986. Graduation, 1989, 1990, 1991, 1993, 1998. For My Friends in Grade K, 1992-1993 (2 copies). Second grade memories, 1994-1995. Class of 1995 (2). Through the Years, class of 1992 and class of 2003.
    - Midtown Ethical - fourth grade plays, 1985-1999 (Offsite-box 275)
      Oliver, 1985 and 1996. Trumpet of the Swan, 1986. Wind in the Willows, 1990. The Wizard of Oz, 1997 (2). You're a Good Man Charlie Brown, 1999 (2).
    - Midtown Ethical - performances and other, 1990-1998 (Offsite-box 275)
      Ancient Festival, 1990. 3P plays, 1991. 5FG Roman Gods, 1997. Jason and the Golden Fleece, 1997. The Trial of Zeus, 1998 (2). Sixth grade recital, 1998.
    - Fieldston Lower - closing assemblies, graduating classes, 1994-2008 (Offsite-box 276)
      Class of 1994. Graduation, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2003, 2004 and 2005. Step Up Day, 1999.
    - Fieldston Lower - performances and other, 1989-1999 (Offsite-box 276)
      Daisy tape, 1989-1993. Snake Festival, folk singer, Russian story teller, 1990. Medieval Fest, 1991. Medieval Fest/A Joyful Noise, 1991. Songs and Dances of Many Lands, 1991/1992 and 1993. Various, 1992. Song and Dance Assembly, 1992. Various, 1992/1993 (3). Sixth grade, 1993. Science 1992/Islamic calligraphy 1994. Various, 1994 (3). Dinosaur recital, 1995. Cecilia, 1995. Grade 5 plays, 1995. Second grade prehistoric animal songs, 1996. First grade birds of prey, 1997. Dino Song Sharing, 1997. City and Country, 1997. Welcome Assembly, 1998. Grade 2 Dinosaur, 1998. Fifth grade medieval festival, 1999. Second grade dinosaur songs, 1999 and 2000. Fourth grade biographies, 1998 and 1999. Bill Robinson bird show, 1999. Music Reunion, 1999. Fourth grade egg drop/recital, 1999.
    - Fieldston Lower - performances and other, 2000-2007, undated (Offsite-box 277)
      Norse myths, 5B 2000. Fourth grade biographies, 2000 and 2003. B Fairy Tales, 2000, 2001, 2002. Fourth grade egg drop day, 2001. World Music Assembly, 2001 and 2002. Norse play rehearsals, 5B 2002. 5B and K Norse Myths, 2004. Immigrant panel, 2005. Cinco de Mayo, 2006. Fifth and Sixth grade concert, 2007. Wolf Assembly, 2007. Westchester Philharmonic Copland Millennial Commission, undated. Garnevicus - music, undated. Betty, undated. 5-6's R, undated.
    - Unidentified lower school, 1983-2007 (Offsite-box 277)
      Wizard of Oz, 1983. Oliver, fourth grade play, 1985. Fifth grade Ancient Festival, 1986. Ancient Fest Olympic Games, 1987. Charlotte's Web, fourth grade, 1988. Colonial plays, 1988. 5-6 Math, 1993-1994. 1F and Step Up Day, 2007.
    - Second grade recitals, 1992-1994 (Offsite-box 277)
      Second grade recital/1st grade owl crow, 1992. Second grade recital, 1993/Dinosaur songs, 1994.
    - Third grade recitals, 1993-2006 (Offsite-box 277)
      1993/1994, 1995, 1999, 2006.
    - Fourth grade recitals, 1995-2001 (Offsite-box 277)
      1995 (2), 1996-1997, 2000, and 2001.
    - Fourth grade recitals, 2002-2006 (Offsite-box 278)
      2002 (2), 2003, 2004 (2), 2005 (2), 2006, and 2007.
    - Fifth grade recitals, 1997-1999 (Offsite-box 278)
      One tape, with fifth grade recitals 1997 and 1999.
    - Sixth grade recitals, 1992-2006 (Offsite-box 278)
      1992, 1995 (2), 1996, 1997 (2), 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002, 2003 (3), 2005(2), and 2006.
    - Evening concerts, 2002-2006 (Offsite-box 278)
      2002 (2), 2003 (2), 2005, and 2006. Some with programs for 5th and 6th grade Fieldston Lower student concerts.
    - World Music Assembly, 1994-2007 (Offsite-box 278)
      1994, 1996, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2004, 2006, and 2007.
    - Harvest Festival, 1990-2007 (Offsite-box 279)
      Harvest Festival 1991, 1992, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2003, 2004 (2), 2005, 2006, 2007. Snake/Apple Fall Festival, 1990. Harvest Festival 1992/Festival of the Animals 1993. Fieldston Lower School Harvest Festival, 2000.
    - Martin Luther King Day Assembly, 1991-2007 (Offsite-box 279)
      1991, 1993, 1994 (2), 1995 (2), 1996 (2), 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001 (Fieldston Lower), 2002, 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006, 2007.
    - Book Awards, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 279)
      "Chelsea and the Green Haired Kid," skits and interview with author, 1988. "Matilda," 1989.
    - Holiday Assembly, 1985-2006 (Offsite-box 280)
      Holiday Assembly 1985, 1986, 1987, 1988, 1989, 1990 (2), 1991 (3), 1992, 1993 (2), 1994, 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002, 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006. Ethical Culture School Christmas Assembly, 1985. Ethical Culture School Holiday Assembly, 1989 (2), 1992. Holiday Assembly/6th grade recital, 1989. Holiday Assembly 1990/Thanksgiving 1991. Fieldston Lower School Holiday Assembly, 2000.
    - Earth Fair, 1995, 2000 (Offsite-box 280)
      1995 (2), 2000.
    - Jazz programs, 1981-2001 (Offsite-box 280)
      Jazz assembly 1981. Jazz assembly, 1984. Fieldston Jazz Spain tour, 1985. Jazz concert, 1986 (Beta cassette). Fieldston jazz improv concert, 1994, Jazz concert 2001.
    - Thanksgiving, 1991-2006 (Offsite-box 281)
      Thanksgiving 1991/1992 and 1995. Thanksgiving Assembly 1993, 1994, 1996, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2002, 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006. Fieldston Lower Thanksgiving Assembly 2000 and 2001.
    - Fieldston, 1992-1998 (Offsite-box 281)
      Fieldston 1992 (2). Fieldston class of 1993 (2, including Farewell). Fieldston class of 1998. Fieldston - May 8, 1998.
    - Fieldston graduation, 1985-2000 (Offsite-box 281)
      Labeled graduation or commencement. 1985, 1990, 1994, 1996 (2), 2000.
    - Graduation - school unknown, 1985-1997, undated (Offsite-box 281)
      Graduation tapes labeled 1942, 1985, 1988, 1991, 1992 (2), 1993, 1994 (2), 1996 (2), 1995, 1997.
    - Fieldston yearbook, 1992-2002 (Offsite-box 282)
      Labeled yearbook or video yearbook. 1992, 1993, 1994 (2), 1995, 1996, 1998, 2002. Nine undated tapes. One unlabeled, undated tape.
    - "Broadway" shows, 1997-2006 (Offsite-box 282)
      1997, 2000, 2001, 2002 (2), 2003, 2004 (2), 2006, undated.
    - Fieldston drama, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 282)
      Fiddler on the Roof, 1981. Guys and Dolls, 1982. Senior play, 1983. Anything Goes ["Much of it has no sound/last section has no sound"], 1983. You Can't Take It with You, 1986. Cabaret, 1989. Form IV dramatization "Nosotros Sonos Dios"/Form I musical program, 1989. Sweeney Todd, 1990 (2). Noises Off, 1990. Little Shop of Horrors, Act 1 and Act 2, 1992.
    - Fieldston drama, 1991-1996, undated (Offsite-box 283)
      The Diviners, 1991 (3). The Crucible, 1992. Inherit the Wind, 1992. Into the Woods, Act 1 and Act 2, 1992. Spring Cabaret - Safer Sex, 1992 (2). The Heidi Chronicles, Acts 1 and 2, 1993. A Flea in Her Ear, 1994. Music Man, Part 1, 1994. The Miracle Worker, Act I and Act 2, 1995. Macbeth, Act 1 and Act 2, 1995. Women and Wallace, 1995 (2). The Seagull, Act 1 and Act 2, 1995. Cabaret, 1995. Spring Cabaret, 1995. Habeus Corpus, Act 1, 1996. Witness for the Prosecution, 1996. Studio Theater Series, 1996. Sex, Drugs, and Rock and Roll, 1996. Habeus Corpus, 1996. The Diviners, undated (2). Lost in Yonkers, undated. A Thousand Clowns, undated (4).
    - Parent and Teacher Association, 1989-1998 (Offsite-box 283)
      Parent and Teacher meeting, "Why we teach the way we do," 1989. Media and children, 1993 and undated. Michael Thompson parent meeting, 1998.
    - Fieldston dance concerts, 1983-2000 (Offsite-box 284)
      1983, 1985 (2), 1986 (New York Moves), 1987 (2), 1988, 1989, 1990 (4), 1992 (2), 1993 (winter concert), 1995, 1999 (2), 2000.
    - Fieldston spring dance concerts, 1989-2006 (Offsite-box 284)
      1989, 1991 (Parts 1 and 2), 1993 (2), 1996 (3), 1997, 1998, 1999, 2001, 2002 (2), 2003 (2), 2004 (2 videos, plus empty case), 2005, 2006.
    - Fieldston Dance Company, 1991-2004 (Offsite-box 285)
      1991 (Lehman College), 1991 (assembly), 1992 (3 videos), 1994 (Alvin Ailey Dance Project, 2), 1995 (Tour, Columbus High School), 1995 (Student choreography). FDC Project, 1999. The Paul Taylor Project, 2001. Various, 2002. The Ailey Project, 2003, The Robert Battle, 2004 (2). Various, 2004.
    - Fieldston dance, 1993-2001 (Offsite-box 285)
      Fieldston Dance Company with Regent Family Residents/Fieldston assembly Dance Out Project, 1993. Dance concert assembly, 1993. DanceWorks, 1993. Martha Graham Project, 1996. Dancespace Project, Young Dancemakers Project, 1999. Nelson Ave Dance Out Project, 2000. Dance documetary, 2001. Various, 2001.
    - Development, 1987-1997, undated (Offsite-box 285)
      Ethical Culture Fieldston Campaign: Making a Difference, undated (4 copies, possibly different versions). Endowment Campaign Training Session, 1987. Endowment presentation, 1989. Ethical Culture Fieldston Campaign: Making a Difference - New York Society for Ethical Culture, 1997.
    - Historical, undated (Offsite-box 285)
      Earlier materials that have been reformatted to VHS. (Date of reformatting unknown.) Ethical Culture School Camp, 1930-1948 (2 copies) - "movie made at the camp in 1936. Every camper appears in the film." 1942 Graduation. "Lewis Hine - LP. Charlotte's Web, fifth grade, 1974. Daedelus Production, taped from TV," undated.
    - Mark Edwards and Company, 2006 (Offsite-box 286)
      Four tapes, dated April 28, 2006. 1. "Mission and Purpose." 2. "Lev." 3. "Franci." 4. "Stewardship."
    - Fieldston Enrichment Program, 1995, undated (Offsite-box 286)
      Two copies of undated tape. Two copies of 1995 program graduation.
    - Unlabeled, undated (Offsite-box 286)
      Six tapes with unintelligible or missing label.
    - Various, 1982-1989 (Offsite-box 286)
      Space launch landing, 1982. Indian cookout, 1985. Spanish V - panel discussion, 1985. Winter holiday program, 1986. Spring concert, 1986. Leonardo's Children "Ethical Culture Schools, " 1986. Holocaust assembly, 1987. Earl Robinson/Snake Festival, 1989. Teaching to Children's Learning Styles and Abilities, 1989. Assembly - French music, 1989.
    - Various, 1990-1994 (Offsite-box 286)
      Halloween Tate Library pumpkin contest, 1990. S. Bonnet class, 1990. City and Country, 1993 and 1994. John Hendricks: The Freddie Sessions, 1993. Pat Norman: A Celebration, 1993. Apple farm video brochure, 1993. Drew Harvey memorial, 1994. Early Music Ensemble, 1994. Ron Taffel, 1994. Dallas Symphony Orchestra, 1994. Silverweed Picnic, 1994 (2). Intro to Community Service, 1994. Girls soccer, 1994.
    - Various, 1995-1999 (Offsite-box 287)
      Eddie Palmieri, 1995. International Folk Dance, 1997. 1995 and 2000 History Tour (part of Env. Fair). Methodist Church Home, 1998. Ron Toffel - Parent to Child, 1998. Mr. Ellis, 1999. Yugoslavia assembly, 1999.
    - Various, 2000-2005 (Offsite-box 287)